[Music]
my name is Kip sson I'm the chief people
officer at Journey team Journey team is
a Professional Services consulting firm
specializing in Microsoft Technologies
well I think the talent Gap has affected
many ecosystems including BC as a
consulting firm we've had substantial
growth roughly 30% or greater over the
last few years and finding the right
Talent with the right skill sets whether
both technical or even on the business
side has always been a struggle for us
to grow and ultimately to serve our
clients I'm Greg crle i'm the Erp
practice director for Journey team for
us res skill was the answer we looked at
doing it internally uh but for the cost
and the professionalism that they've
brought it aligns directly with our
principles and our culture so teaming
together has really been a benefit in
moving this forward there are a limited
number of people with BC experience
today with consultant skills and
identifying a new source that we could
tap into it's key to our growth I think
the BC Community needs the next gen of
talent pretty much so we can continue to
innovate but if we don't have a strong
connection to the business requirements
and the business needs we're going to
miss the boat res skill is part of our
growth strategy because we're trying to
identify people with industry experience
who understand the processes teach them
the technology the BC knowledge and how
to be a better consultant the value of
the professional skills training it is
addressing the gap on the mindset and
behavioral side of Consulting not just
the technology side and as technologist
we have a tendency to just double down
on skill sets around technology and we
Overlook what are the soft skills and
the professional skills required to
ultimately serve our clients I would
recommend rescale to other partners look
at look at what you're trying to
accomplish if it fits the culture you're
after uh it's very efficient from a cost
perspective from a Time perspective it
was very quick to get this rolling uh I
would recommend it I think other
partners should join because it's a
no-brainer so I think what we've gained
in this program so far is an increase of
technical knowledge but most importantly
this expectation and Clarity of how we
need to show up as consultants to better
serve our
[Music]
clients